Sseu-eup, private bastard
I'm in a hurry
The sound of rolling eyes
I can hear you from here, private!
- Private Park Yoon, Private Park Yoon...
- Private, Private
- Private, Private Park Yoon-seung!
- Bigger than me, private, private.
Private Park Yoon...
Hey, recruit, are you feeling a little nervous right now?
you over there
Do you see the man going home over there?
A whopping 1 year and 6 months
While hitting a hit and run
You're going home now, huh?
how is it? Are you a little jealous?
no
honestly, honestly
Yes, yes! I envy you!
Oh, I'm jealous too, fuck
Hey, but what should I do?
You have an army, huh?
will never come
It's that kind of day, why?
The Earth will be destroyed before then
Isn’t that right, Sergeant Lee Jae-yoon?
Oh my!
Look at me, that socialite smile
I'm so fucking jealous
Loyalty!
loyalty
Report! Sergeant Lee Jae-yoon
As of June 18, 2026
I was ordered to be discharged
I report this
Ouch! insect! castle!
Loyalty!
Lee Jae-yoon has had a hard time so far.
Thank you!
Don't get sick when you go out and live well
Yes, I understand!
Then
pain
Yonseok
Yeongju!
Yeongju
uh? Yeongju!
uh?
Yeongju!
Lord...
loyalty
- Be quiet, the kids are awake.
- Yes, I understand.
Hey, wake up Lineho.
Hurry up and get ready for work
yes, i understand
Coming
It's coming
Inho
Wake up, I have to go to work.
Similar American F Back Solo
Wing center retreat angle
The nose is blunt
- Sausage body shape
- Inho.
Round nose, round engine
Beware of alopecia areata
Dad, what?
Thousands of bombers now
It's flying towards us
I think this guy understands this?
yes
How far have you come?
It flew right in front of me
Be careful, you'll bump into it.
Be careful, don't crash...
Corporal Lineho
When did you become a corporal?
Didn't you hear well?
Not yet
Private Lineho!
This guy is so fucking into it, really.
Get ready for work quickly and come out
yes, i understand
Why?
Pick up the phone
Call me one more time this morning
Know that you will never see my daughter again
Tell it to Jaeyoon
Hello?
Hello
Hey, Kang Young-ju, what are you doing?
Uh, Jaeyoon, why?
'why'?
The voice ‘Why’ comes out, now?
Hey, Youngju.
Hey, let's say that's the case with drinking.
No, I suddenly lost contact.
You made people worry
It took a while before I got a call
I'm a man who doesn't even know who he is
No, what are you doing walking around?
What the hell, now?
person on the phone
I think it's probably our assistant manager.
I was very drunk and came to the front of the house
Because you took me there
No, can you take me to the front of the house? A man?
uh? Become so rude
A man brought me to the front of the house...
Hey, Kang Young-joo, what do you think of me?
Are you not doing it at all?
Hey, I always think about you
Um, sorry.
Hey, but Jaeyoon, hey
It's 3 am now
Hey, no matter how wrong I am right now
You called me like this at this hour
It's not right to wake him up and do this.
No, I didn't sleep a wink all night.
I'm worried about you
Okay, okay, okay
I couldn't contact you properly
I'm sorry
I'll wake up tomorrow and explain everything...
Hello? hello?
what? hello? Yeongju
Hello?
Hello, Youngju.
I really do, Mr.
I can't just get over today
What are you doing now?
So
loyalty
Me too today
I don't think I can just get over it
look at me
Do you really want me to cry?
Sergeant Youngman Kim, I ate all my food.
loyalty
May 2, 2025
1st Platoon morning roll call personnel report
Total 9 members, 2 out of 10, current members 7
Outside content, border worker
Reporter and 6 other people excluding 2 people
Ready for roll call
- Rest
rest
With the consideration of Director Jinji
Today is the Fatherland Prayer
Manual gymnastics is omitted.
The colder it gets, the more I shrink
The body is prone to breakdown
Stuck in my room
Don't watch TV
Even if it’s just bare-handed gymnastics, I do it every now and then.
To help you maintain your basic physical strength,
salute
- Loyalty!
Loyalty!
These bastards
Who's still dozing off, this!
Are you not sure?
- no!
When the young guys shrivel up
Squad leader
Sergeant Kim Young-man
Performed 50 laps of the parade ground
Ha...
‘Ha’, ‘Ha’, ‘Ha’?
These bastards...
Do you want to do 80 laps?
- no!
Okay
Conducted 67 laps of the parade ground
- Do it!
With less than ten people
He can't even keep his feet!
Keep pace!
left foot, left foot, left foot
- One, two
- 65 laps left!
three, four
One, two, three, four
- You’re not shouting slogans!
- One, two, three, four
Keep pace!
- one
- Two, three...
“Popoa”
- Hey, Kang Young-ju, let’s go together.
- Hey, Seulgi Choi
It's late, run
- Yeongju
- Senior
- Are you going to work now?
- yes
- Hello
- Yes, it’s been a while, Seulgi.
How is your work life?
Thanks to your advice
I'm adapting very quickly
I never forget grace
Hey, but you
It's been a month since I joined the company.
I always say it’s my fault
Don't just talk like that.
Even a plate of tteokbokki
Please return the favor, junior.
100 plates of tteokbokki
I can buy you more
Yeah? So how about tonight?
today?
Today...
If it doesn't work out today, there's nothing I can do.
Next week is okay too
the door closes
Now the customer
I can't answer the phone
Please contact me again later
Really, Mr.
Anti-aircraft emergency, anti-aircraft emergency, anti-aircraft emergency
Completely dressed up in 5 minutes
Gather at the parade ground
What's the emergency this morning? why?
Loyalty!
This way
Let's get started
conducted
Implement!
7 km in 8 directions, one Mi-4
Approaching the direction of the position
final armament approval
full-on shooting and
We will carry out shoot-down shooting.
7 km in 8 directions, one Mi-4
Approaching the direction of the position
final armament approval
full-on shooting and
Carry out shooting down!
Pick up the high-speed command desk receiver
Press emergency button, wait 3 seconds
anti-aircraft emergency, anti-aircraft emergency
7 km in 8 directions, one Mi-4
Approaching the direction of the position
final armament approval
Full fire rush and shooting down
anti-aircraft emergency, anti-aircraft emergency
7 km in 8 directions, one Mi-4
Approaching the direction of the position
final armament approval
full-on shooting and
Carry out shooting down!
Generator on
Armed connector tentatively coupled!
Gunner Seungpo, Corporal Jeon Hyeong-bae
Lead calculation sight open!
- Turn on the grid power switch
- Turn on the power switch
- Shooting speed 30
Shooting method: Expel radar mock shell once
7km altitude limit in 8 directions
People spread out around the gun
- 7km target captured
- 6km
- 5km beam radiation
- 4km
- 3km
- One, two, aim shooting
- One, two, aim and fire!
Power switch off
- One po, report.
- report
One Mi-4 was shot down.
Number of bullets consumed: 30
Other personnel and equipment abnormalities
good reception
The first ammunition depot opens!
Opening of the 2nd ammunition depot
- 100 shots
- 200 rounds
- 400 rounds
- Complete shooting start!
- One gun, full fire charge completed
One gun, command to fire
Jin...
Blood...
Jinji 1 direction 5km
An- One paratrooper from the 2nd unit...
5 km in one direction of the camp - 2 units per unit
Dropping paratroopers
Vulcan Hana artillery paratrooper shooting conducted
Shinggung aircraft shooting completion report
Report completion of shooting of Shingung aircraft.
- Good reception
- Good reception!
- run
- Turn on the power switch
5 km altitude limit in one direction
People spread out around the gun
- Shooting method manual
- Low speed continuous fire
- Low-speed continuous shooting
- Target speed 0
- Target range 2,000
- Central horde captured
- Step on the foot switch
- Apply gunner lead
One, two, aim and fire
Land, land, land!
- Capturing a group of cattle
- Step on the foot switch
- Apply gunner lead
- One, two, aim shooting
- Land, land, land!
Power switch off
One gun, annihilation of paratroopers was completed.
Number of bullets consumed: 90
Other personnel and equipment abnormalities
good reception
Those two over there
This is our squad ace.
and there
Private First Class Hwang Gyeong-sik, the ammunition commander, also
Last division commander shooting competition
10th round full bloom
I have won
Growing strategically
He is a model soldier in our platoon.
Lieutenant Park Seong-wook
The shrine is over there
Guided missiles completely removed!
bang!
Everyone died! Everyone died!
Those two
I'm a little older than the other kids
twenty-six, thirty
As a result, life in the military
Adapt...
‘Everyone died’, Mr.
Squad leader
Sergeant Kim Young-man
What is our unit's mission?
In preparation for the unexpected appearance of a red flag
The highest view in Seoul
On top of 77A Tower
Create a GOP equipped with anti-aircraft guns
Always on guard
Protecting Seoul’s major facilities
Promoting the safety of citizens
The airspace of the capital Seoul
It's about defending
Go forward
in place
turn back
Today I tell you
really disappointed
Originally, they were all in military training camp.
It's right to send it!
Let’s end it at this level
I'm grateful
As I jumped up to the 77th floor,
What did each of us do wrong?
Think about it carefully
Loyalty!
Just send them to a military training camp.
77th floor
Fuck, why don't you all shut up!
turn back
Go forward
Be careful, be careful, be careful
In order to meet the construction schedule now...
Fuck!
The restaurant is here
We will guide you
This way
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
I'm hopeless
- Go up
- Leave me alone.
Climb up, you bastard.
- Kim Young-man
- Yes
You feel more comfortable now that you’re a sergeant, right? uh?
Hey, kids below you
If you can't manage it
They say I eat up my time with my asshole.
Listen, you idiot.
I'll do well
Fuck you guys, really.
Hey, turn it all over
Hey!
Drop everything!
Fuck, Line Ho, Jaeyoon Lee, really...
Hey, it happened last night.
One kid uses his cell phone while working
Another cub on duty
I fell asleep and fell asleep
That's not enough
Hey, in emergency training
Artillery drops missiles?
And that too in front of the battalion commander?
Fuck, I knew it right away when I saw that.
We're doing it so fucking wrong
Hey, I was the battalion commander, right?
니들 개새끼들아, 씨발
다 영창 보냈어, 어!
As of this moment
No cell phone use under me
If you get caught secretly using it
I killed that bastard
It's a party, so take care of it yourself.
- Hey, Hyeongbae.
- Corporal Jeon Hyeong-bae
- Take your phone away right away.
- Yes, I understand.
Hey, and you two
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
Private Lineho
I'm really lazy
I didn't want to say this
I wish I had joined the military when I was younger.
Pay for the night
You bastards
I woke up late and had to go to work.
I was so distracted that I couldn’t answer the phone.
I'm really sorry about yesterday, Jaeyoon.
At the new employee welcoming party
Because I drank too much
With the assistant manager who lives next door
Because the manager is in the same direction
Because you took me there
you have enough
I know this situation can be misunderstood.
But Jaeyoon...
Private Choi Cheol-woo
Private First Class Hwang Kyeong-sik
Won't you come soon?
Private Lineho
- Go and stand
- Yes, I understand.
fuck you bastard
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
- Huh?
- Let go
- Well, for a moment
- Let go.
- uh? Corporal, wait...
- Let go
This is a really important contact...
Fuck, hey, Jaeyoon Lee!
Won’t you let it go quickly?
fuck now
Who am I doing this for?
Are you out of your mind?
sorry
- Loyalty
- Loyalty!
Why is the atmosphere in the dormitory like this?
I'm scared so I can't come in
What is this?
Private Choi Cheol-woo
Even though you spin so hard
Do you want to exercise again?
Why is it so thick?
Doing the upper body on the same day as the lower body
It's natural.
Ah, I'm tired just looking at it.
Our Cheolwoo
Later, my brother will eat chicken.
I'll give you something boiled, come to the restaurant
Corporal Kwak Gye-young
Thank you!
Kwak Gye, your cell phone is also confiscated.
Yes? Yeah, whatever
Do whatever you want as it doesn’t even ring.
instead
One cooking support person
Please
I have to go deliver again
How long do I have to live like this?
Look at that bastard alone.
I'm into it
Jaeyoon is taking you?
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon!
- Self-catering support
- Yes, I understand!
Come quickly!
Really, Sergeant Jeong and Lieutenant Park
Such absurdity within the unit
Making a fuss about getting rid of it
They are Jjambap just like us
I don't want to eat it
What is it?
Always have me deliver something
Completely naronambul
Wait and see, before I get discharged.
I'm going to hit you hard
Discharge...
You bastard
If you say something old, you have to react.
Isn't it?
sorry
But if you look at it, the problem is the problem
You and Lineho
It's the same today too, just the two of us as a set...
But Lineho is better than me
A few more mistakes...
Why are you in the unit like this?
Can't you adapt?
Inho hyung, just by looking at him, he looks foolish.
Well, he's the oldest.
I can say that, but Jaeyoon, you
Graduated from a prestigious 4-year university
Because he looks smart...
What's wrong?
What's going on outside?
Outside...
What's out there?
no
Well, it's here
What's going on, come quickly
Hey, you bastard
I'm really crazy...
- Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
- Come quickly.
sorry
- Are you Reinho?
- No.
Hey, hurry up
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
Hello, Mr. Sujeong.
Please use those people.
We installed an elevator for you.
If you do this here
VIP guests feel uncomfortable
Oh my, my, you didn't know
That elevator is broken.
Then you have to report the malfunction.
oh my god, we
Your cell phone was also confiscated?
Yes, anyway
Yes, with our guidance
please follow me
yes sorry
No, that's what I mean
Every time something like this happens
To that person in advance
I think I should let you know
If you have a business card, could you give me one?
Mr. Crystal
What are you really saying?
It sounded like a business card and I fell asleep.
really annoying
- Hugeogeuk
- What?
Sujeong was originally like this.
Are you cold to people?
crazy...
Let’s just quickly go do some errands.
You have nothing to do with me.
No
My business was here...
- What did you say?
- Did you remember my name?
Why do I remember your name?
It's written here, 'Kwak Gye-young'
I don't think you understand what I'm saying.
- Not once or twice...
- Sorry, just a moment.
- Hey, Jaeyoon.
- Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
Aaron Park has emerged, the legendary Aaron Park.
Quickly bounce, bounce, bounce!
- There, there, there!
- Aaron Park, Aaron Park!
Those bastards
The Legendary Aaron Park
I almost got caught, that bastard really
- We were talking well.
- Kabi, Kabi
Hey, let's do something quickly and let's go
yes, i understand
hello
- Hey, Paulo!
Even a tiger says what he says
They said they were coming, huh?
It's amazing
Shall I cut some meat?
tomorrow evening
There's a Korean dinner, so look forward to it.
- Dinner? really?
- Hello Jaeyoon?
Then tomorrow evening
I'll solve it here
Me too, me too, me too, me too
Korean traditional jars are cool
This is not a jar
Uh, um, um, um, ‘ttukbaegi’
Earthen pot?
Shintobuli
Corporal Kwak Gye-young
To Chef Jeong
I have some business to do...
- Hang up within 5 minutes
- Yes, I understand.
If I'm late, boss Jeong
I know how shitty it is...
- Yes, I understand!
- That bastard
Ongojishin
here
Feel free to use it, Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon.
I have this grace
I won't forget until I die
Thank you!
Thank you
Mr. Youngju
I think I got a call
No, hey, this is shrimp
I already ate it all
Hello
Hey, Kang Young-ju!
You said you would stand up and explain.
But I’m not even answering the phone!
Oh, you're Jaeyoon?
Whose cell phone is this?
No, that's not important now
I'm really angry?
you keep going like this
You're going to skip it, really?
Hey, you were drunk yesterday
You don’t even remember talking to me on the phone?
Right?
Hey, I was there earlier.
You sent it all in a message.
With a few letters like that,
Just trying to get over it, that's...
Youngju, you really are
Not sure what the problem is?
Yeah, hey, yesterday I...
Jaeyoon, Boss Jeong
They're looking for me, I have to go now.
- Otherwise, I'm going to the brig!
- Yes, I understand!
- I'll call you right back.
- Hey
Explain it straight then, okay?
Hey Jaeyoon Lee
That boyfriend who is in the military?
yes
What is your rank now?
Private first class
It's still far away
But are you going to wait?
Hey, why do you talk like that? huh?
Is Youngju an idiot?
I'm not even going to get married
Why wait for that? It's a waste of time
Isn't it?
Is that so?
- Really, why are you doing that, really?
- Right.
Mr. Youngju
If you love your boyfriend a lot
waited
You could get married, right?
Right, Mr. Youngju?
Yeongju is with her boyfriend.
Are you planning on getting married?
I got there
Because I didn't think about it...
Wait a minute
Youngju, you have to think now.
No...
Youngju, you are just getting older.
You're not young.
What's wrong?
Why am I like this?
Mr. Youngju, what I mean is
Youngju is now
I'm old enough to think about such things.
That's what I mean, joke, joke
Yeah, you should think about it, age
I'll take care of it.
Enjoy your meals
I feel a bit sick
Yes, enjoy.
Hello?
Private Jae-yoon Lee
Can I talk to you on the phone?
Oh my, what should I do?
Jaeyoon returned to the unit earlier.
yes, i understand
yes
Ugh
Hey, Lineho!
Private Lineho
Where have you been, this bastard?
I have to separate it now.
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
This
Hey, you bastard
Didn’t you pay for this earlier?
I'm in a hurry
What is it? Is this mine?
To the administrative supply officer, the baby is
I said I was sick and received it.
Is your baby sick?
I'm not sick, I'm healthy
I think you need Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon.
Instead of mine
I changed it to Private Lee Jae-yoon’s.
cub
What are you going to do if you get caught with this?
amazing bastard
Thank you, father
Hey, Rheinho, Rheinho!
-Private Lineho!
- Replacement
- Replace!
- Yes, I understand!
Line ho!
quickly go to the warehouse
Talk to your girlfriend
Today, me and Private Hwang Kyung-sik
I'll handle it
yes, thank you
Replace!
Hold it like this...
Next is the news
Today, everywhere in Seoul
Citizens suffering from seizures
Incident of attacking a passerby
It happened again
Ministry of Health and Human Services
We are closely monitoring this phenomenon.
The citizens are quarantined...
I came
What is it? What is this ambiguous time?
In preparation for any possible infectious disease...
It doesn't even seem like I went somewhere to play.
Playing around
I came back from working overtime, mother.
I'm really hungry, give me food
Did you talk to Jaeyoon?
If you call me one more time at dawn
Mom won't stay still
I don't know, I don't know, I don't remember anything
If you are a person with an idea
Don't call me like that at night
Hey, you really think carefully.
If you meet such a selfish bastard
I'm going to live my whole life suffering.
Seriously, why is everyone like this these days?
One real call
Hard to do, right?
So
Yeongju
I saw the text you sent
The new employee welcoming party
The assistant manager who lives next door
I can understand all that.
But I was in the military
I can't do anything and it's a bit frustrating.
Can't you be a little more considerate?
I'm worried about you here
It's because it's so hard
Hello?
hello? Yeongju
- Jaeyoona
- Huh?
How about we take some time?
Well...
What are you saying all of a sudden?
Hey, I nagged you a little bit.
Are you doing this now?
no
I said you nagged me
It's not like this
What is it then?
After you go to the military
I honestly thought about it a lot
Is it right for me to wait for you?
Okay, let's say I waited 1 year and 6 months.
And then what about us?
you and me
What next?
Look, Jaeyoon.
Even on the last day of your military service
don't worry about me
He didn't say a word
Even now my questions
You can't answer until the end
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
- Uh
- Sergeant Youngman Kim is looking for you.
I'll be there soon
- Okay.
- I'll be right away, I'm out.
Jaeyoona
You're not the only one having a hard time
Okay, I'll do whatever you say.
- Eat.
- Mom!
Just knock and come in!
what? why are you crying
I'm not crying
Can I just say one thing?
- No, don't.
- Private Lineho
yes, i understand
Try it, what is it, dad?
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon, are you okay?
No, the lord
Let's take our time, okay?
Hey, this
You're saying we're breaking up, right?
May I say one more thing?
When we're alone, it's just like that.
You can talk without asking, it's okay
yes, i understand
Then I have a question for you
I'll give it to you
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon is discharged from the military.
Are you going to marry your girlfriend?
Well, what
Youngju with me
Will you do it for me?
I didn't even graduate from school
Then your girlfriend
until when
Should I just wait?
Waiting for a year and a half
It won't be easy
my wife did that
If it weren't for my son Hayul
I think he would have abandoned me a long time ago.
Our cutie Youngman
What should I buy you when you come?
No, me too
next week
He said he would let me go down.
Go get something delicious
Come eat plenty, Loyalty
You bastard is like this again, again
I'll buy a hamburger when I come back.
six
hit and run
- seven
- Please enter
eight
nine
heat
Hey, do it in moderation.
It's crazy, kinda
Just one more set
Let me finish
Lee Jae-yoon and Line Ho
Yesterday's work log
I didn't write it right, damn it.
Anyway, let me catch Wang Go.
난 이 새끼들 진짜로
그냥 이렇게 안 냅둬, 씹새끼들
니 말은 즉 왕고인 내가 잘 못해가
자들이 저카는 거라고 들린다
왜 말씀이 또 그리로 튑니까?
Our Sergeant Youngman Kim
My favorite character in military life
You know that you are my role model, right?
You speak well, huh?
By the way, Jaeyoon and Inho
What should I really do?
Fuck, I don't know, huh?
They are definitely older than us.
Wow, doing it right
Don't you have any?
Here's our good A-list son.
Even if they look half the same
I don't have to worry
Right, Kyungsik?
Private First Class Hwang Kyung-sik, yes, that's right.
What's wrong with that?
Hey, isn’t Jaeyoon your old friend?
- Hwang Kyeong-sik
- Private First Class Hwang Kyeong-sik
This is ‘doing well, doing well’
So he just leaves
Do you have no ups or downs?
Go to the beauty salon
Wouldn't it be better to just do it?
Hygienically and cosmetically
I said I couldn't do it.
When my boyfriend goes to the military
It was my wish to try this.
I am better than other soldiers
I'll shave it off nicely
Going
What should I do?
Is it fun?
- Cute, cute, pretty
- Are you laughing?
cute
It's ugly, don't do it
Don't do it, it's ugly.
That ugly guy is your boyfriend
you watch this alone
Also, don’t show it to anyone else.
Got it?
Do it quickly
Suddenly?
Are you crying?
I want to stop
Hey
Hey, hey, what if I just leave like this?
Hey...
Don't do it, it's ugly.
That ugly guy is your boyfriend
you watch this alone
Don't post it anywhere else...
Yes, senior Jinwook.
What, why are you like this?
Is your voice bad?
It's been a while since I woke up
What did you call about over the weekend?
Because I ran errands for my father in the morning.
After crossing Gangbuk
I'm done with my work here.
But when I saw it
This is the neighborhood right next to yours.
so now i
Youngju, it’s in front of your house.
Yes? In front of my house?
uh? It was good
Yeongju
Have you waited long?
no, no
I came here suddenly
Just by meeting you like this
I'm so sorry, uh
Let's go, while I wait
I made a reservation at a suitable place nearby.
here is my friend
You come here often because you have a stake in it?
But here
Dinner is better than lunch.
It's really nice here, sir.
It's really delicious here
I'll order this as a course.
Yes, senior.
Anyway, senior
When I got a job
You helped me so much
Now I'm finally repaying the favor like this.
I'm sorry and thank you so much
But I'll return the favor later
Because it's expensive here
I'll just live today
No, sir, I will live here.
It’s okay, so buy tteokbokki next time
Hey, and you and me
How many years have I known you?
Are you still a senior?
Just in private
Feel free to call me oppa
I have an unnecessarily strong personality
If we start to match like that
There is no end
So you can't do it.
I'm finally laughing a little
While coming by car
He didn't say a word
What happened?
Boyfriend problems?
That's right
After the department event, we have a company dinner.
I didn't see you because you went first then.
Junho got drunk like this
I kicked the department chair in the stomach.
The head of the department is in his 60s, so...
Shouldn’t you get that?
He's my boyfriend
If I get it now
I think the call will be long
You can call me again when you get home later.
yes
Well, anyway
Hey, I'm you
I never imagined I would work an office job.
A pretty girl
I go to practice every day
Fixing the machine
I was so amazed
I am that famous
Isn’t this the engineering goddess Kang Young-joo?
Ha, but like that
Living with oil on your face
My mom really hated it.
Well, I just
I also wanted to live a normal life
So thank you to my senior.
I told you to call me oppa
You try ‘oppa’
If you do that carelessly
I can't do it.
Try ‘oppa’
senior
- Hey, is that difficult?
- No, no.
Please return it for me
You're catching him like you're catching a rat.
all day
Well, to a kid who is 10 years younger than me.
Just swearing
Anyway, the team leader
The language is too harsh
- Me, senior.
- Huh?
I need to go to the bathroom for a moment...
Uh, uh, okay, I went and came.
There is one voice message
Uh, Yeongju, it’s me, Jaeyoon.
First of all, I
I'm sorry
I'm in your shoes
When I thought about it
Well, there really was no answer.
We are twenty-six now
I will be twenty-seven when I am discharged from the military.
I still have to graduate from school
I also need to prepare for employment.
The military is also the military.
After being discharged from the military, without any promises
Asking me to wait
I don't think that makes sense
Honestly, I want to be like this in my future too.
I'm not sure
I think that's so selfish
And well, under the pretext of loving you
It's just like this
I wanted to pretend not to know
It's the same
So I don't think that will work
for you
you and me, for each other
Yeongju
Let's break up now
Thank you so much, Youngju.
I'm sorry, really
stay healthy
The power is off
Voicemail after beep...
Youngju, what are you going to ride?
That taxi
See you at work next week then.
Yeongju!
I'll take you to the unit.
So what about elevator repairs?
Should I call after getting it?
I was told to call the machine room.
I was calling
So
How long have you been on the phone now?
It's been over a week
yes, yes
Anyway, it's not their business.
To be complacent
Even if I send just these two
Are you okay? Especially this one...
Private Lineho! You can do it well!
I'm really anxious
Now Sergeant Ahn Seong-gyu and Sergeant Yoo Byeong-jun.
Until I return in the evening
The kids are working full time.
Except Lee Jae-yoon and Line Ho.
There is no one to buy oil
If something happens
You have to go catch them yourself.
Okay?
yes, i understand
Did you hear?
Don't do anything useless
Just buy gas at the intersection gas station
Return to the unit right away, okay?
all right!
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
Are you okay?
Where is the private bastard?
Do you wear your hat at an angle?
- Hey
- Private Lineho
Don't overdo it, I'm fine
Okay then
Get some donuts with this
Can't I buy it and come back?
If you eat sweets
It makes you feel a little better.
Amazing, amazing, huh?
When did you get that and this again?
Let's eat, okay
What's left is to eat
I guess this is
Because it’s in the middle of Gangnam
- There are a lot of business customers.
- Teacher, teacher!
Hello, Mr. Sujeong.
yes, teacher
Even if it's an inconvenient part...
Yes?
no
Last time, our senior
I think I told you
Our private elevator was broken.
We know that
If you keep coming down like this...
I definitely told that senior
I think I made my point clear.
That Kwak-gye... Young?
You remember my name.
Yes, sir, how can I help you...
‘Asia Superstar Awards’
Isn't it true?
At 4 p.m.
Sponsor representative
When will you arrive?
Why, well, well, even the teacher
Do you have any business?
I know your representative well.
Let me say hello
Industry trends so far
Let's talk about this...
Hey, you bastard, what's wrong with you?
Have you lost your mind?
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
Do you not know Alex Enter?
You know, you know
- I told you last time.
- Yeah, you did.
- Hey!
- The representative there...
Two military barbarians!
I'm just asking this because I'm curious.
Youngju you are now
Are you going to break up?
How long until we arrive?
We're all here
yes
But it’s Yeongju.
no matter what happens
When times are hard, my brother is always there
Don't forget that I'm by your side
As I always did
Like a big tree next to you
So that you can lean on me
I'll be waiting
yes, yes
For now, yes
No, why on earth
Come only during my working hours
Is this what you are doing?
I...
Excuse me
Sorry, sir.
I'll be there soon!
Really
Private First Class Lee Jae-yoon
- Can I just say one thing?
- What is it?
There is no more time to delay
I don't think there is one
Then we
-If you can't eat donuts...
- Hey
What is that?
- He's coming.
- Hey, why are you flying this way!
- It's work!
-Private Jae-yoon Lee!
Coming!